welcome to the second video on CSS today
ยินดีต้อนรับสู่วิดีโอเรื่องที่สองของ CSS ในวันนี้
we're going to look at changing the font
เราจะดูการเปลี่ยนแบบอักษร
color the font type in the font size and
สีแบบอักษรในขนาดตัวอักษรและ
so let's go ahead and use the source we
ดังนั้นเราจะไปข้างหน้าและใช้แหล่งที่มาของเรา
did from the last video and let's open
ทำจากวิดีโอล่าสุดแล้วลองเปิดดูสิ
that up now now you will remember that
ตอนนี้คุณจะจำได้แล้ว
we created our first rule and that we
เราสร้างกฎข้อแรกของเราและเรา
decided to go ahead and style the h1
ตัดสินใจไปข้างหน้าและมีสไตล์ h1
HTML element right here and we gave it a
องค์ประกอบ HTML ที่นี่และเราให้
background color of purple and so let's
สีพื้นหลังของสีม่วงและเพื่อให้ของ
just go ahead and take a look at that
เพียงแค่ไปข้างหน้าและดูที่
again and there you can see we have our
อีกครั้งและที่นั่นคุณจะเห็นเรามีของเรา
purple background now what I want to do
พื้นหลังสีม่วงตอนนี้สิ่งที่ฉันต้องการจะทำ
is create a new role so let's go ahead
คือการสร้างบทบาทใหม่ดังนั้นเราจะไปข้างหน้า
and do that and so we just do the same
และทำแบบนั้นและเราก็ทำแบบเดียวกัน
thing we did with the h1 rule we'll just
สิ่งที่เราทำกับกฎ h1 เราจะเพียง
copy and paste that and we're going to
คัดลอกและวางข้อมูลนั้นและเราจะไป
go ahead and style the P HTML element so
ไปข้างหน้าและรูปแบบองค์ประกอบ P HTML ดังนั้น
that's right here this one everything
นี่คือทุกสิ่งทุกอย่างที่นี่
within here and everything within here
ภายในที่นี่และทุกอย่างภายในที่นี่
now what I want to point out is we said
ตอนนี้สิ่งที่ฉันต้องการจะชี้ให้เห็นคือเรากล่าวว่า
H 1 here and that equated to the h1
h1 นี่และเท่ากับ H1
header when you put in P here and just P
ส่วนหัวเมื่อคุณใส่ใน P ที่นี่และเพียง P
we are going to alter everything all of
เราจะแก้ไขทุกอย่างทั้งหมด